Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 7: Firestone Scholarship Program For Sons and Daughters of Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 8: Pension and Insurance Plan for Hourly - Rated Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 9: Firestone Short Term Disability Benefits Plan For Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 10: Firestone Scholarship Program For Sons and Daughters of Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 11: Pension And Insurance Plan For Hourly-Rated Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 12: The Firestone Tire & Rubber Company An Announcement of Improvements to the Employee Benefits Program For Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 13: Employees Personal Insurance Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 14: Employee Benefits For Regular Full Time Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 15: Personal Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: You, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Firestone Employee's Handbook, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: Employmee Assessment Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 4: Major Medical Plan Improved Prescription Drug Benefits, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 5: Major Medical Plan Improvement Prescription Drug Benefits and Other Major Medical Benefits Plan Revisions, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 6: Announcing Improved Firestone Retirement Plan & Major Medical Plan For Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 7: Firestone Employee's Handbook, Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Firestone Non-Skid, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: Firestone Non-Skid, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Historical Highlights The Firestone Tire & Rubber Company, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 4: Firestone Non-Skid, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
    March 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Firestone Non-Skid, Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Firestone Non-Skid, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: Firestone 1967 Annual Report, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Firestone Non-Skid, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Firestone Non-Skid, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    January 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Firestone Non-Skid, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: Historical Highlights The Firestone Tire & Rubber Company, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 7: Firestone Suggestion System Operating Manual, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 8: I Speak for Democracy, Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    By Elizabeth Ellen Evans. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: A Career in Investment Banking with The First Boston Corporation, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Training Program Temporary Departmental Assignment Letter, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Application for Employment, Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Annual Report To Stockholders for the year ended December 31, 1959, Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Employees Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: Employee Security and Benefit Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
    October 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Group Insurance Protection for You, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Item 4: Personal Data Sheet, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Item 5: To all members of the Retirement Plan of The First Boston Corporation, Publication (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The First Page, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: About Our Bank, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Glimpses Behind the Scenes, Publication (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Outlook for Business For the las six months of 1970, Publication (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Ourlook for Business For the last six months of 1971, Publication (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Outlook for Business For the last six months of 1971, Publication (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Outlook for Business for the first six months of 1969 by The First National Bank of Boston, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: The Outlook for Business for the last six months of 1968 by The First National Bank of Boston, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: The Outlook for Business for the last six months of 1968 by The First National Bank of Boston, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Gold and the Balance of Payments, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Outlook for Business, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
    December 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Outlook for Business, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 7: Outlook for Business, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 8: Outlook for Business, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 9: The Outlook for Business for the first six months of 1969 by The First National Bank of Chicago, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 10: The Outlook for Business for the last six months of 1969 by The First National Bank of Chicago, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 11: The Outlook for Business for the last six months of 1969 By The First National Bank of Chicago, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 12: Gold and the Balance of Payments, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Item 13: Outlook for Business For the first six months of 1971, Publication (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: First National Bank 1965 Annual Report, Publication (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Communicator, Publication (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Communicator, Publication (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: Communicator, Publication (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Communicator, Publication (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Communicator, Publication (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: You and the 1st, Publication (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Annual Report To The Staff Building In '61 For Your Future And Ours, Publication (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Item 2: First National Bank of St. Louis Annual Report 1964, Publication (Box 14, Folder 28)
    February 5. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: First Pennsylvania Bank/The Profits of Change, Publication (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Profit Sharing Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Retirement Benefit Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: The New Banking Programs For Executive Development, Publication (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Audit of Internal Communications, Publication (Box 14, Folder 30)
    May 30. Item is in English.
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Personnel Policy Manual, Publication (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: How would you like to work for one of the nation's most progressive Banks?, Publication (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Item 2: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Item 3: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 14, Folder 33)
    January 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: You and our Company, Publication (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Item 5: Company Rules & Regulations, Publication (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Item 6: Employees' Handbook, Publication (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Item 7: Management Review and Recommendations, Publication (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Item 8: Management Review Work Sheet, Publication (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Item 9: Employees' Handbook, Publication (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Hospitalization and Sick Benefit Plan Pension Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 2: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 3: Incentive Savings Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 4: Salaried Personnel Policies And Procedures, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 5: Incentive Savings Program, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 6: Pension Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 7: Massachusetts mutual Life insurance Company, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 8: Pension Plan Disability and Sick Benefit Plan For Employees, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 9: Summary of F&P Salaried Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Item 10: Your Group Life and Major Medical Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: The First Word, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
    May 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The First Word, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
    April 26. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The First Word, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Item 4: The First Word, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
    September 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The First Word, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
    August 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The First Word First happenings, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
    August 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Social Scorecard, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
    By James F. Bodine. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: To My Associates, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
    By James F. Bodine. January 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Dear Fellow Employee, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Item 10: First Pennsylvania In The News, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Item 11: First Pennsylvania In The News, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Item 12: The First Pennsylvania Banking and Trust Company Annual Report, December 31, 1964, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Item 13: Packet, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
    May-June. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Policy No. 20 Education Tuition Allowance, Publication (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Agreeement between Fisher & Porter Company Alloy Steel Casting Company Warminster Fiberglass Company and Independent Union of Rotameter Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Agreement Between Fisher & Porter Co. Alloy Steel Casting Co. and Independent Union of Rotameter Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Item 3: Agreement Between Fisher & Porter Co. Alloy Steel Casting Co. Warminster Fiberglass Co. and Independent Union of Rotameter Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Item 4: Agreement Between Fisher & Porter Co. Alloy Steel Casting Co. and Independent Union of Rotameter Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Item 5: Agreement Between Fisher & Porter Co. Alloy Steel Casting Co. and Independent Union of Rotameter Workers, Publication (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Box: 14, folder: (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Welcome to Fischer and Porter, Publication (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Item 2: The Newsrator, Publication (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Item 3: The Newsrator, Publication (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Item 4: Fisher & Porter Company Annual Report year ended 30 April 1955, Publication (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Item 5: The Newsrator, Publication (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Item 6: The Newsrator, Publication (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Item 7: Annual Report/1957 Fisher & Porter Company, Publication (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Box: 15, folder: 1 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
    January 30. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Agreement, Publication (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Flexonics Newspaper, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Flexonics Newspaper, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Flex-O-Gram, Publication (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Your Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: for your family and future Flexonics Profit Sharing, Publication (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Report to The Public Shippers Of Freight Recievers of Freight and Passengers, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Senate Gets Facts on FEC and duPont Estate, Publication (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: State of Florida Mediation & Conciliation Service, Publication (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Continuous Announcement of Career Opportunities With State Agencies Served by the Florida Merit System, Publication (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Your Company and You, Publication (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Organization Chart #21, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Application For Employment, Publication (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: FYI, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: current, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: current, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: current, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: sunshine service news, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Sunshine Service News, Publication (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: $ For Your Bright Idea$, Publication (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Faculty Handbook, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: FSU and You, Publication (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A Co-Operative Plan of Group Life Accident and Health and Hospital and Surgical Insurance, Publication (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Story of Food Fair Stores, Inc., Publication (Box 15, Folder 13)
    October 22. Item is in English.
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Pride & Progress, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    May/June. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Pantry Press, Publication (Box 15, Folder 14)
    March-April. Item is in English.
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1964, Publication (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Food Fair Stores Foundation Scholarship Program, Publication (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: You And Food Fair, Publication (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: You And Food, Publication (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Employee Suggestion Form, Publication (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Employees Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Group Hospitalization Insurance, Publication (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Putting Ideas to Work, Publication (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: fmc progress, Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: fmc progres, Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: fmc flask, Publication (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: The apprentice experts, Publication (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Program in Economic Development & Administration 1965, Publication (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Skills, Scholarship and the Public Service, Publication (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Your Suggestion Plan Guide, Publication (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Suggestion Plan, Publication (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Management Proposal Plan, Publication (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: "Suggestion System --- Democracy In Action", Publication (Box 15, Folder 24)
    By R. E. Roberts. November 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Suggestion Plan Flow Chart, Publication (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Item 6: Employee Suggestion Section, Publication (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, Publication (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Item 2: Newsletter Members of Community Relations Committees, Publication (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: Newsletter For Members of Community Relations Committees, Publication (Box 15, Folder 25)
    April 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Bulletin, Publication (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Item 5: Bulletin, Publication (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Item 6: Newsletter For Members of Community Relations Committees, Publication (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: The Ford Foundation in the 1960s, Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: About the Ford Foundation, Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Item 3: About the Ford Foundation, Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Item 4: Ford Foundation Grants in Vocational Education, Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Item 5: Skills, Scholarship and the Public Service, Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Item 6: Ford Foundation Grants in Population, Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Item 7: Skills, Scholarship and the Public Service, Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Item 8: The Newsman's Scope, Publication (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Bargaining And Economic Growth, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    June 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Prolonged Strike Costly to Company; Highlights of Settlement Reviewed, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 3: Ford Girds for UAW Pay Push, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    October 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Preparation For Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 5: Management Information Program, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    August 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: To The Men and Women of Ford Motor Company, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    By Henry Ford. August 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Ford Welcomes Vote on Strike, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    By Henry Ford II. August 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: To The Men and Women of Ford Motor Company, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 9: Basic Approaches To Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    By John S. Bugas. July 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: To All Members of Management, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 11: Ford Gives Viewpoint On Labor, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    By A. M. Smith. April 29. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: a letter to Walter Reuther, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    By Henry Ford. August 24. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Immediate Release, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 14: Unionization of Foremen At Ford Motor Company, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    By William T. Gossett. February 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Industrial Relations-Unfinished Business, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    By John S. Bugas. April 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Union Monopoly vs. The Public Interest, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    By Ernest R. Breech. January 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Basic Approaches To Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 18: Memorandum, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 19: Bargaining And Economic Growth, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    By Henry Ford. June 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Benefit Plans and Agreements Ford Motor Company and the UAW, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 21: Agreements between Ford Motor Company and the UAW, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 22: The Ford Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 23: Immediate Release, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Item 24: Intra-Company Communication, Publication (Box 15, Folder 29)
    September 20, 1958. Item is in English.
- Box: 15, folder: (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Index, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 2: Supervisional Training, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 3: Salaried Personnel Exit Interview, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 4: Executive Communication, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 5: Application For Employment Technical, Professional and Managerial Personnel, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 6: going places with information for salaried employes, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 7: Welcome To Ford Motor Company, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 8: going places with Ford information for salaried employes, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 9: Welcome To Ford, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 10: Salaried Personnel Application For Employment, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 11: Marketing at Ford, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 12: Expanding Your Horizons With Ford, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 13: Going Places With Ford, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 14: Your Future With Ford, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 15: Employee's Withholding Exemption Certificate, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 16: Salaried Employee Performance Review, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 17: Salaried Personnel Performance Appraisal Of Production Supervision, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    May 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Industrial Arts Awards, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 19: Staff and Division Personnel Concerned With Industrial Relations Activities, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 20: Safety Program, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 21: Ford Motor Company Organization Manual, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 22: Information Sheet, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 23: Industrial Relations Staff, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 24: Organization Manual Statement of Functions, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 25: Hourly and Salaried Personnel Military Leave, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 26: Salaried Personnel Change In Status, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 27: Salaried Personnel Change In Status, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 28: Position Specification, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    May 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Dear Miss Jacobson, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
    By S. W. Scott. March 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: Salaried Personnel Application For Employment, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 31: The Challenge of industrial Opportunity, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 32: setting your course, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 33: Inudstrial Relations Reference Material, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 34: So You Want To Be A Test Driver!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 35: So you want to work in Finance!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 36: College Graduate Employment Application, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 37: So you want to be an Engineer!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 38: So you want to be an Auto Service Technician!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 39: So you want to be an Automobile Salesman!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 40: So you want to be a Stenographer!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 41: So you want to be a Stylist!, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 42: Looking Ahead, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 43: Total Performance Since 1903, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Item 44: Ford Motor Company, Publication (Box 15, Folder 30)